<news>
  <item>
    <id>184</id>
    <title>Download your Free Launch Spacesuit and Follow @LittleBigPlanet on Twitter for your chance to Win a Rare LittleBigPlanet Cap! </title>
    <summary>LittleBigPlanet PS Vita is out now and to celebrate the occasion, we have re-released the Launch Spacesuit onto the Store for a limited time only.

We don&apos;t want to stop the celebrations there though!

So this weekend we will be holding a small contest on our @LittleBigPlanet Twitter feed to give people the chance to win one of our very special Rare LittleBigPlanet Caps!

You will need to download your free Launch Spacesuit to be able to enter though, so head on over to the Store and pick it up right away!

Then just be sure to be following us on Twitter to find out the full details on how to enter tomorrow.

Twitter: @LittleBigPlanet</summary>
    <text>LittleBigPlanet PS Vita is out now and to celebrate the occasion, we have re-released the Launch Spacesuit onto the Store for a limited time only.

We don&apos;t want to stop the celebrations there though!

So this weekend we will be holding a small contest on our @LittleBigPlanet Twitter feed to give people the chance to win one of our very special Rare LittleBigPlanet Caps!

You will need to download your free Launch Spacesuit to be able to enter though, so head on over to the Store and pick it up right away!

Then just be sure to be following us on Twitter to find out the full details on how to enter tomorrow.

Twitter: @LittleBigPlanet</text>
    <date>1348755214000</date>
    <image>
      <hash>4947269c5f7061b27225611ee58a9a91a8031bbe</hash>
      <alignment>right</alignment>
    </image>
    <category>no_category</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <id>86</id>
    <title>LBPC Contest #7 Winners</title>
    <summary>The LittleBigPlanet Central Contest Crew are pleased to showcase the winners of their &quot;It&apos;s Showtime!&quot; contest in this brand new hub level!</summary>
    <text>&lt;slot type=&quot;user&quot; id=&quot;23247537&quot; icon=&quot;b953fa35fcb96cc78e9a8e831e9f6d390c14a1a8&quot; big=&quot;true&quot;&gt;LBPC7: It&apos;s Showtime!: Winners Hub&lt;/slot&gt;

Find out more about this recent contest and how you too can enter future LBPCentral contests over on www.lbpcentral.com</text>
    <date>1334060091000</date>
    <image>
      <hash>f3a79d207c4c7a6fb71b981e569d7f1cc4cf1d24</hash>
      <alignment>right</alignment>
    </image>
    <category>no_category</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <id>28</id>
    <title>We have taken the score boards offline for some maintenance.
</title>
    <summary>They will be down for a few weeks, during which time&lt;b&gt;no scores will be saved to the servers&lt;/b&gt;. You will still be able to play story and community levels and get a score, they just won&apos;t be uploaded and kept on file. </summary>
    <text>Hi Sackfolk! 

We have taken the score boards offline for some maintenance.

They will be down for a few weeks, during which time&lt;b&gt;no scores will be saved to the servers&lt;/b&gt;. You will still be able to play story and community levels and get a score, they just won&apos;t be uploaded and kept on file. 

Sorry about that, everything will return to normal as soon as possible, we promise!</text>
    <date>1308580104000</date>
    <image>
      <alignment>left</alignment>
    </image>
    <category>no_category</category>
  </item>
  <item>
    <id>11</id>
    <title>LBP.me - Discover the Community on the web!</title>
    <summary>Did you know that you can view all your levels and your activity on the internet? Weâve built a brand new website http://lbp.me on which you can browse all of the wonderful creations on the LittleBigPlanet.</summary>
    <text>&lt;b&gt;Change your Privacy settings&lt;/b&gt;

If you want to see your stuff appear on the internet, you will have to change your privacy settings! They are currently set to off, and we will wait for you to give us permission before we publish anything of yours on to the web.

&lt;b&gt;To change your settings&lt;/b&gt;
â¢ Press Start
â¢ Go to Settings
â¢ Find the Web Privacy settings
â¢ Choose if you would like your profile and your levels visible to no one, everyone, or just people who log in
â¢ Now go to http://lbp.me and log in to see your page!</text>
    <date>1295545154000</date>
    <image>
      <alignment>left</alignment>
    </image>
    <category>no_category</category>
  </item>
</news>